<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Delightfully Discombobulated]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Delightfully Discombobulated]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/delightfully-discombobulated/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 03:44:31 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/delightfully-discombobulated/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cleaning Heaven???]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Cleaning Heaven???</h1><p>Okay...I'll admit it.  I'm the Queen of the Clorox wipe.  So I laughed at my neighbor when she started talking about the non-toxic cleaners that she had been guilted into trying by another friend who is turning slightly crunchy.  (Don't get me wrong...I'm all for saving the Earth, but cloth diapers are not in my vocabulary.) </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/delightfully-discombobulated/cleaning-heaven/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9a3d042d-a917-415b-9537-fd32f2496c55</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 03:43:49 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Forgotten Friend]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Forgotten Friend</h1><p>I talked you through your darkest hours. </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/delightfully-discombobulated/forgotten-friend/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c796d538-a3c8-4c23-a099-6662800d9ee8</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 03:43:40 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Autism Safety - Oxymoron]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Autism Safety - Oxymoron</h1><p>This weekend was a conundrum of major safety issues.  Friday evening we went to eat with friends who also had children.  The noise inside seemed to really bother Reagan, so we sat on their large covered / mostly enclosed porch area.  When we got ready to leave,  I took him out of his highchair and reached to grab the bag of fidget toys.  Something spooked him, and he took off running and screaming, almost making it to the parking lot.  Choosing the lesser of two evils, I tripped my 3 year old child.  Trust me when I say this was not a proud moment.  It really scared me horribly, as you can imagine.  There was no warning at all.  </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/delightfully-discombobulated/autism-safety-oxymoron/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">e50c91c3-5e23-447f-8981-62c66dabee9f</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 03:43:31 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[I Won an Ipad!]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>I Won an Ipad!</h1><p>I attended the vendor area of the Autism Conference that was held in Dallas this week as I could only go for part of one day with Patrick's work schedule.  It was a bit disappointing not to be able to attend sessions, but I was at least able to learn more about services offered for children like Reagan.The kicker is that the day after attending, I received a phone call asking if I was still at the conference.  I explained that I was not because I lived in the Dallas area.  They asked if I could come back to the conference and pick up an item I won in a drawing - an iPad!!!   I said that I probably would be able to do that despite having said many times that an iPad is nothing but a glorified iPhone that's bigger and doesn't make phone calls.  Let's just say, I stand corrected!  This thing ROCKS!  It's now loaded up with awesome apps for Reagan that are completely geared toward children with autism!  They even made sure they were at his functioning level!  While I did the PR interview and photos, Chance was snagged by the group next to us.  It was the people from Google!  (Not just anyone....it was the big guns!)   They had chosen to launch a new product called SketchUp, kind of like "ketchup" with an S added to the beginning.  They had Chance play with it while they talked the audience gathered around about the program and how user-friendly it is.  (I guess the point was that it was so user friendly even a 2nd grader could do it?  Someone should inform them that I have a crazy smart 2nd grader!)  It seemed like a pretty big deal, and I wish I had been able to get pictures or a video of him doing the demonstration with them.  I think it's pretty awesome of Google to launch something at an autism conference.  That's a pretty nice vote of confidence for our kids!Here is the newsletter from the company who gave us the iPad. It's called WellSpring, and they provide in-home ABA services in California and now Florida.  They hope to launch in Texas at some point.  I told them to let me know because Frisco is the place they need to have their Texas headquarters, right?</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/aa453ea2edd2f3f2fa8ca6e20b8fadad278bf078.tiff"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/delightfully-discombobulated/i-won-an-ipad/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">65120960-dc35-4dc9-83d2-0065280ad61f</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 03:43:07 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Starting Over Again]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Starting Over Again</h1><p>Reagan loves his new Early Childhood School!  Our only issue so far has been morning car ramp.  They are about to have to do some staff training (at my request, actually) because they have some staff members who, in the past, worked with typical kids and don't seem to get that a child in a SLC classroom doesn't always follow verbal directions or make eye contact ESPECIALLY if the staff member is unfamiliar.  We have had to modify Reagan's drop off procedure for a few weeks to avoid complete meltdowns that included laying on the concrete and refusing to move.  (and staff members telling him to look at them and listen to their instructions.)  That has been the ONLY issue, though!  He does love it there and is always excited to see the building.  He loves his teacher and one of the aides.  The other one they are still working on him responding to her at all.  His class will be full next week with the addition of one more boy.  That will be 5 children with 3 adults!  Yippee!!!!</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/delightfully-discombobulated/starting-over-again/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">27d036c0-7e97-4f64-b026-fd8bf82c062d</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 03:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>